BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series VI: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
  - Code no.2371: J.H. France Refractories, Harbison, Kaiser and UBC, 1979-1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Code no.4611: Armstrong (Lancaster floor plant) and Rubber Workers, 1972-1986 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Code no.8898: National Concrete & Building Products Agreement and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1973- 1982 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Code no.560446: B.F. Goodrich Chemical Group and Distillery Workers, 1973-1982 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Code no.561710: Boise Cascade Co. and UBC, 1983-1986 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Code no.571248: Dresser Industries and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1990 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Code no.580020: International Paper Co., Androscoggin Mill and United Paperworkers' International Union, 1970-1987 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Code no.590437: Brown Co. and United Paperworkers' International Union, 1971-1980 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Code no.590755: Ciba-Geigy Corp. and OCAW, 1971-1990 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Code no.590898: St. Regis Paper Co. and United Paperworkers' International Union, 1975-1982 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Code no.590996: Dow Chemical Co. and UFCW, 1978-1981 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Code no.591193: General Refractories Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1977-1987 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Code no.591240: Chevron United Steelworkers Association Inc. and OCAW, 1963-1993 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Code no.591361: Lumber & Mill Employers Association and UBC, 1967-1990 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Code no.591449: ITT Rayonier Inc. and IAM, 1974-1980 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Code no.591749: Occidental Chemical Co. and International Chemical Workers, 1976-1987 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2313: Glass Container Industrial Relations and American Flint Glass Workers Union of North America, 1971-1990 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2363: Owens-Brockway Packaging Co. and Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers, 1986-1993 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Code no.6325: Northern IL Ready Mix and Materials Association and IBT, 1972-1995 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Code no.1006: Weyerhaeuser Co., Wood Products Group and International Workers Association, 1969-1988 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Code no.1211: Hammermill Paper Co. and United Paperworkers' International Union, 1972-1986 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Code no.1212: Hudson Pulp and Paper Corp. and United Paperworkers' International Union, 1971-1992 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Code no.1213: Georgia Pacific Corp. and Office and Professional Employees International Union, 1993-1996 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Code no.1300: Champion International Corp. and United Paperworkers' International Union, 1980-1986 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Code no.1411: Chicago Lithographers Assoc. and Graphic Arts International Union, 1974-1991 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Code no.1630: Dow Chemical Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1992 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Code no.1663: BASF Corp. Fibers Division and United Textile Workers of America, 1971-1995 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Code no.1664: Allied-Signal Corp., Fibers Division and IBT, 1972-1993 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Code no.1683: PPG Industries and IAM, 1973-1982 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Code no.1900: Pirelli, Armstrong tire Co. and Rubber Workers, 1985-1991 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Code no.1903: Firestone Tire & Rubber Co. and Rubber Workers, 1982-1985 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2315: Owens-Illinois Inc. and Flint Glass Workers, 1971-1992 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2453: Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corp. and IBT, 1974-1992 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Code no.8318: Rock Products & Ready Mixed Employers Association and IBT, 1967-1997 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    1967-1990, 1994-1997
- Series VII: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.7: General Dynamics, Convair Division and IAM, 1972-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Code no.8: Hughes Aircraft Co. and IAM, 1972-1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Code no.9: Lockheed Missiles & Space Co. and IAM, 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Code no.10: Martin Marietta Aerospace and UAW, 1972-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Code no.16: Olin Corp. and IAM, 1972-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Code no.21: General Dynamics, Pomona Division and IAM, 1972-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Code no.26: Westinghouse Electric Corp., Aerospace Division and IBEW, 1970-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Code no.27: ICI Americas, Inc., Indiana Army Ammunition Plant and IBEW, 1972-1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Code no.28: Mason & Hanger, Silas Mason Co., Iowa Ammunition and IAM, 1966-1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Code no.38: Day & Zimmerman Inc., Lone Star Division and International Chemical Workers, 1978-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Code no.1101: NAP Consumer Electronics and IUE, 1981-1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Code no.1102: Kroehler Manufacturing Co. and United Independent Union, 1971-1983 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Code no.1103: Simmons United Steelworkers Association and United Independent Union, 1979-1994 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Code no.1105: Upholstered Furniture Manufacturers Association and United Independent Union, 1970-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Code no.1106: Upholstered Furniture Manufacturers Association and IUE, 1970-1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Code no.1107: Upholstery Employers Association and United Independent Union, 1972-1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Code no.1108: GF Business Equipment Inc. and United Steel Workers of America, 1968-1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Code no.1112: Eastern Products Corp. and International Telecommunications Union, 1970-1985 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Code no.1113: Hamilton Industries and UBC, 1970-1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Code no.1120: Georgia Pacific Corp. and International Telecommunications Union, 1972-1986 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2131: Chicago Rawhide Manufacturing Co. and UFCW, 1970-1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2500: Interlake Inc. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2502: Allegheny Ludlum Industries and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2504: Armco Inc. and Independent, 1971-1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2505: Armco Steel Corp. and Independent, 1971-1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2506: Armco Steel Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1968-1983 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2507: Atlantic Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1993 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2508: Babcock & Wilcox and United Steel Workers of America, 1974-1991 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2509: Standard Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2510: Bethlehem Steel Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1974-1983 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2512: CF & I Steel Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Code no.2514: Continental Steel Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2516: Copperweld Specialty Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2520: Cyclops Corp. and N/A, 1971-1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2523: Great Lakes Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2524: Inland Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2526: Jones & Laughlin Steel Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2527: Jones & Laughlin Steel Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2530: Laclede Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2531: Lone Star Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2532: Lukens Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2534: Weirton Steel and Independent, 1971-1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2535: Northwestern Steel & Wire Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Code no.2538: Wheeling Pittsburgh Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1999 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2539: Republic Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2540: Sharon Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1968-1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2544: US Steel (P & M) and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2545: US Steel (Off, Tech, & Prof) and United Steel Workers of America, 1974-1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2547: Elkern Metals Co. and OCAW, 1973-1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2550: Universal Cyclops and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2551: Wheeling Pittsburgh Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2555: American Steel Foundries and United Steel Workers of America, 1968-1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2557: Blaw-Knox Equipment Inc. and United Steel Workers of America, 1968-1987 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2558: Buckeye Steel Castings and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2567: Mead Corp. Lynchburg Foundry and United Steel Workers of America, 1967-1993 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2572: Dresser Industries, Transportation Equipment Division and United Steel Workers of America, 1973-1984 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2573: Campbell Wyant and Cannon Foundry Co. and UAW, 1971-1990 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2575: Mirodot Inc. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2576: Amax Copper Inc. and United Steel Workers of America, 1980-1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2582: Kennecott Copper Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2585: Ormet Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2586: Phelps Dodge and United Steel Workers of America, 1974-1983 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2590: Aluminum Co. of America and UAW, 1977-1983 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2591: Aluminum Co. of America and Aluminum, Brick, and Glass Workers, 1971-1983 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2592: Aluminum Co. of America and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1986 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Code no.2597: Bridgeport Brass Co. and Independent, 1971-1980 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Code no.2603: Huntington Alloys, Inc. and United Steel Workers of America, 1973-1983 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Code no.2604: Kaiser Aluminum and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2605: Mueller Brass Co. and UAW, 1972-1981 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2609: Revere Copper & Brass Inc. and Mechanics Educational Society, 1971-1990 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2610: Reynolds Metals Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2611: Reynolds Metals Co. and Aluminum, Brick, and Glass Workers, 1971-1989 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2612: Reynolds Metals Co. and Aluminum, Brick, and Glass Workers, 1974-1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2613: Western Electric Co. and Independent, 1974-1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2614: NL Industries Inc., Doeler Jarvis Castings Division and UAW, 1974-1986 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    1974-1980, 1983-1986
  - Code no.2618: Ladish Co. and IAM, 1973-1994 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2619: Mclouth Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2622: Latrobe Steel Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1983-1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2624: Stockham Valves & Fittings and United Steel Workers of America, 1964-1985 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2626: Racine Steel Castings and UAW, 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2627: Moore Co. and Independent, 1974-1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2628: Phoenix Steel Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1965-1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2629: Aluminum Company of America and Aluminum Trades Council, 1971-1992 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2631: Cerro Copper & Brass Co. and UAW, 1966-1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2633: Dayton Malleable Iron Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1965-1980 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2634: Martin Marietta and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2643: Engineers and Scientists of California Corp. and Independent, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2654: Wyman-Gordon Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1983 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Code no.2655: National Steel Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Code no.2658: American Insulated Wire Co. and IBEW, 1973-1982 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2659: Wagner Castings Co. and Industrial Workers, 1971-1996 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2660: National Standard Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1974-1989 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2664: Manufacturers' Industrial Relations Association and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2665: Wheland Foundry and United Steel Workers of America, 1988-1992 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2666: Teledyne Wah Chang Albany and United Steel Workers of America, 1977-1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2670: Harman International and UAW, 1976-1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2671: Al Tech Specialty Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2900: American Can Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1981 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2902: American Can Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1977 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2903: Continental Can Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1986 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2904: Continental Can Co. and IAM, 1971-1986 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2905: National Can Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1989 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2906: Emhart Industries and IAM, 1973-1988 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2907: Keystone Consolidated Industries, National Lock Division and UAW, 1977-1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2908: Stanley Works and IAM, 1973-1991 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2909: True Temper Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1990 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2912: American Standard and Independent, 1975-1986 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2920: Trane Co. and IAM, 1970-1982 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2923: Babcock & Wilcox and Boilermakers, 1969-1982 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Code no.2926: California Metal Trades Council and IAM, 1974-1989 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2927: Combustion Engineering Inc. and Boilermakers, 1970-1990 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2930: Hollow Metal Door and Buck Association Inc. and UBC, 1970-1988 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Code no.2931: California Metal Trades Association and IAM, 1968-1992 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2936: US Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1987 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2941: Commercial Shearing Inc. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2942: Mirro Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1991 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2948: WM. Powel Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1969-1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2952: Western Steel Council and Association of Bridge, Structure, Ornamentals, and Iron Workers, 1971-1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2957: Kohler Co. and UAW, 1968-1980 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2965: ITT Grinnell Corp. and IAM International Molders and Allied Workers, 1972-1987 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2969: Crown Cork & Seal Co. and United Steelworkers Association, 1971-1989 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Code no.29641: Slanadyne Inc. and UAW, 1971-1983 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2972: Southern California Steel Fabricators and Boilermakers, 1973-1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Code no.2973: Norris Industries and UAW, 1972-1982 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Code no.2974: Wire & Metal Products Manufacturers Guild Inc. and IBT, 1978-1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2978: Foster Wheeler Corp. and IAM, 1971-1989 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2980: Master Lock Co. and IAM, 1971-1983 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2983: Diebold Inc. and Boilermakers, 1971-1983 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2988: Stroh Container Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1977-1990 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2990: Magic Chef. Inc. and Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers, 1980-1988 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2994: West Bend Co. and Independent, 1973-1988 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Code no.3200: White Industrial Power and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1981 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Code no.3203: Briggs & Stratton Corp. and International Workers Association, 1971-1986 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Code no.3204: United Technology, Elliott Co. Division and United Steel Workers of America, 1977-1999 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Code no.3206: Teledyne Continental Motors and UAW, 1971-1983 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Code no.3207: Cooper Energy Service and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1992 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Code no.3208: Cumming Engine Co. and Diesel Workers, 1972-1993 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Code no.3210: Colt Industries and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Code no.3212: OMC. Waukegan (Johnson Outboard) and Independent, 1977-1992 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Code no.3214: Worthington Compressors and United Steel Workers of America, 1974-1980 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Code no.3216: Fiat-Allis Construction Machinery, Inc. and UAW, 1971-1985 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Code no. 3222: Deere and Company and UAW Locals 450, 94, 865, 1536, 81, 74, 434, 838, 1974-1986 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Code no.3230: Bucyrus Erie Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1973-1991 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Code no.3231: Cameron Iron Works and IAM, 1971-1989 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Code no.3233: Caterpillar and IAM, 1977-1980 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Code no.3236: Hamischfeger and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Code no.3237: Hughes Tool Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1968-1992 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Code no.3242 Dresser Industries, Marion Power Shovel Division and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1987 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Code no.3245: Brown & Sharp Manufacturing and IAM, 1973-1981 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Code no.3246: Chandler Evans Control Systems and UAW, 1974-1992 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Code no.3258: Beloit Corp., Paper Machine Division and IAM, 1979-1993 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Code no.3264: Rockwell International, Reading Foundry and United Steel Workers of America, 1975-1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Code no.3265: USM Corp., Beverly Machine Division and IUE, 1978-1981 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Code no.3268: Dresser Clark Inc. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1989 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Code no.3269: Fafnir Bearing and UAW, 1970-1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Code no.3273: Ingersoll-Rand Co. and IUE, 1972-1985 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Code no.3274: FMC Corp., Bearing & Chain Division and United Steel Workers of America, 1982-1988 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Code no.3275: MRC/TRW, Marlin Rockwell Division of TRW and UAW, 1971-1977 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Code no.3278: Timken Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Code no.3287: Sperry-Rand Corp., Univac Division and IBEW, 1976-1984 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Code no.3291: Admiral Corp. and IAM, 1973-1976 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Code no.3292: York International, Applied Systems and UAW, 1973-1996 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Code no.3293: Chrysler Corp., Airtemp Division and IUE, 1971-1982 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Code no.3294: Copeland Corp. and IUE, 1970-1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Code no.3298: Ford Aerospace and IUE, 1972-1987 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Code no.3305: Washington Metal Industries and IAM, 1974-1985 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Code no.3310: Wein Industries and United Steel Workers of America, 1974-1990 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Code no.3311: Carrier Corp. and Sheet Metal Workers, 1971-1985 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Code no.3313: New Idea Farm Equipment Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1984 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Code no.3314: Tecumseh Products and IAM, 1968-1983 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Code no.3315: Ingersoll-Rand Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Code no.3322: Danly Machine Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1977-1988 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Code no.3324: Burroughs Corp. and UAW, 1971-1986 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Code no.3326: Cessna Aircraft and IAM, 1970-1988 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Code no.3328: Dentz-Allis Corp. and United Steel Workers of America, 1974-1989 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Code no.3330: Leesona and IAM, 1975-1979 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Code no.3334: O.M.C. Evinrude and United Steel Workers of America, 1973-1990 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Code no.3342: Diamond Chain and United Steel Workers of America, 1974-1981 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Code no.3360: Reed Tool Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Code no.3368: Paris Manufacturing Co. and UAW, 1971-1986 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Code no.3369: Sperry Rand, Sperry-Vickers Division and Allied Industrial Workers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Code no.3380: John Deere Horicon Works and IAM, 1964-1992 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Code no.3381: New Britain Machine Co. and IAM, 1970-1982 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Code no.3382: Chrysler Outboard Corp. and Allied Industrial Workers of America, 1970-1982 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Code no.3383: Hesston Corp. and Independent Hesston Corporation Workers Association, 1970-1988 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Code no.8898: Stanley Structures and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1973-1982 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Code no.3385: Stanadyne, Western Division and UAW, 1971-1983 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Code no.3387: Allis-Chalmers, York Division and IAM, 1971-1992 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Code no.3393: Carrier Air Conditioning Co. and Sheet Metal Workers, 1973-1985 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Code no.3396: Hyster-Danville and Independent, 1974-1994 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Code no.3604: McGraw-Edison, Power System Division and United Steel Workers of America, 1970-1986 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Code no.3607: Roper Appliances, Kankakee Division and Various, 1972-1981 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Code no.3609: Allen-Bradley Co. and IUE, 1967-1979 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Code no.3614: Cutler-Hammer Inc. and IAM, 1971-1988 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Code no.3618: General Electric and IUE, 1960-1979 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Code no.3621: Rubbers & Myers and UAW, 1971-1981 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Code no.3622: Stackpole Carbon Co. and IUE, 1960-1990 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Code no.3633: Feeders Corp., Norge Co. Division and IAM, 1971-1984 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Code no.3637: Maytag Co. and UAW, 1971-1977 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Code no.3642: Whirlpool Corp. and IAM, 1970-1991 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Code no.3643: Arrow-Hart and IBEW, 1967-1981 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Code no.3647: NY Lamp & Shade Association and IBEW, 1972-1988 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Code no.3649: Admiral Corp. and IBEW, 1969-1975 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Code no.3665: Zenith Radio Corp. and Independent Radio Workers, 1972-1987 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Code no.3667: GTE Automotive Electric and IAM, 1973-1985 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Code no.3668: GTE Communications Systems and IBEW, 1970-1991 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Code no.3670: CTS Corp. and UAW, 1971-1989 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Code no.3677: Teletype Corp. and Technical Employees International Union; Independent, 1977-1983 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Code no.3678: Western Electric, Kearny Works and IBEW, 1974-1986 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Code no.3680: Western Electric, Indianapolis Works and IBEW, 1974-1986 (Box 35, Folder 2)